Summary

I'm a fourth-year coterminal student at Stanford studying Symbolic Systems with a concentration in artificial intelligence, and Computer Science with a concentration in computer systems. In my time at Stanford, I've published research in cognitive science, taught introductory computer science, and am currently researching deep learning in healthcare settings. I spend my free time drawing on my iPad, writing notes in my digital garden, and dreaming up new ways for humans and computers to interact.

Education

Stanford University Stanford, CA

B.S. IN SYMBOLIC SYSTEMS (AI), M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE (SYSTEMS)

Sept. 2017 - Jun. 2022 (expected)

• GPA: 3.79 / 4.00

Columbus Academy Gahanna, OH

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA Aug. 2013 - Jun. 2017

• GPA: 4.52 / 4.00

Work Experience _____

Amazon Fire TV Gahanna, OH (virtual)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2020

- Developed a web portal with React.js and Typescript that now serves as a hub for Fire TV partner communications.
- · Worked closely with engineers and manager to design intuitive, user-friendly workflows for data entry and verification.
- Integrated with backend services at Amazon; deployed on an AWS stack using ECS Fargate, Amazon Cognito, and Amplify.

Stanford Partnership in Al-Assisted Care

Stanford, CA

RESEARCH ASSISTANT Jan. 2020 - present

- Working under Prof. Fei-Fei Li and Dr. Nirav Shah to design automated mental health assessment tools.
- · Developing unsupervised deep learning models in Pytorch to predict depression from patient interviews.

CS 198 Teaching Program Stanford, CA

SECTION LEADER

- Taught weekly discussion section and office hours for 3+ quarters of CS 106B (programming abstractions.) · Worked with sectionees to create elegant, efficient solutions to data structures and recursion problems.
- Held weekly, 1-on-1 code feedback sessions with 30 students, graded over 100 assignments.

Language and Cognition Lab

Stanford, CA

Jan. 2019 - present

Oct. 2018 - Jun. 2020 RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- · Worked under Prof. Michael Frank to analyze first-person infant headcam videos using computer vision algorithms.
- Used face and pose estimation algorithms to compute trends in social scenes over the first 2 years of life.
- Work was accepted for and presented at Conference of the Cognitive Science Society 2020.

Projects

Org-Twitter

Smart Glove $link \rightarrow$

RASPBERRY PI-POWERED SMART GLOVE TO CONTROL IOT DEVICES. WON AWARD IN INTERHACKT HACKATHON.

2020 link →

EMACS PACKAGE TO TWEET SNIPPETS AND THREADS DIRECTLY FROM YOUR ORG-MODE NOTES.

2020

Autonomous RC

 $link \rightarrow$

SELF-DRIVING RC CAR THAT CAN NAVIGATE NOVEL MAZES OF PAPER.

2018

Skills

Advanced Python, PyTorch, TypeScript, React/NextJS, C/C++

Intermediate Neo4j, Lisp, Bash, Swift, Java